<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshop 2018 on Esube Bekele</title>
    <link>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2018/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workshop 2018 on Esube Bekele</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Esube Bekele</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 19:35:39 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://esube.github.io/workshop/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CFP 2018</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2018/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2018/cfp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The second Black in AI event will be co-located with &lt;a href=&#34;https://nips.cc/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;NIPS 2018&lt;/a&gt; at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://congresmtl.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Palais des Congrès de Montréal (Montreal Convention Centre)&lt;/a&gt;  in Montréal CANADA on December 7th from 1:00pm to 6:00pm. The workshop will feature invited talks from prominent researchers and practitioners, oral presentations, and a poster session. There will also be socials to facilitate networking, discussion of different career opportunities in AI, and sharing of ideas to increase participation of Black researchers in the field. We invite all members of the AI community to attend the workshop. The early registration deadline for the conference is October 24, 2018. We strongly encourage workshop attendees to register for the workshops as early as possible. The registration can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://nips.cc/accounts/login/?next=/Profile&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizers 2018</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2018/organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2018/organizers/</guid>
      <description>Workshop Co-Chairs Rediet Abebe, Cornell University
Esube Bekele, US Naval Research Laboratory
Sarah Brown, Brown University
Mouhamadou Moustapha Cisse, Google AI
Timnit Gebru, Microsoft Research
Judy Wawira Gichoya, Oregon Health and Science University
Devin Guillory, Etsy
Sanmi Koyejo, University of Illinois, Urbana Champaigns
2018 Program Committee    Name Institution / Company     Rediet Abebe Cornell University   Dhaval Adjodah MIT Media Lab   Yoseph Berhanu Alebachew Addis Ababa University   Justice Amoh Dartmouth College   Amar Ashar Berkman Klein Center for Internet &amp;amp; Society   Sileye Ba Dailymotion   Esube Bekele US Naval Research Laboratory   Ayalew Belay Addis Ababa University   Danielle Belgrave Microsoft Research   Irwan Bello Google Brain   Samy Bengio Google Brain   Basiliyos Tilahun Betru National Advanced School of Engineering University Of Yaounde I   David Bindel Cornell University   Sarah Brown Brown University   Diana Cai Princeton University   Mouhamadou Moustapha Cisse Google AI   Alexis Cook Udacity   Hal Daumé III Microsoft Research / University of Maryland   Lucio Dery Stanford / Facebook   Ousmane Amadou Dia Element AI   Victor C Dibia IBM Research   Adji Bousso Dieng Columbia University   Awa Dieng Duke University   Charles Earl Automattic   Ashley Edwards Georgia Institute of Technology   Oluwaseun Francis Egbelowo University of the Witwatersrand   Ruth Fong University of Oxford   Sorelle Friedler Haverford College   Lanke Frank Fu Ascent Robotics   Timnit Gebru Microsoft Research   Judy Wawira Gichoya Oregon Health and Science University   Gebremedhin Fisseha Gidey National Advanced School of Engineering University Of Yaounde I   Solomon Gizaw Addis Ababa University   Ian Goodfellow Google Brain   Christan Grant University of Oklahoma   Ben Green Harvard University   Alvin Grissom II Ursinus College   Devin Guillory Etsy   Bernease Herman University of Washington   Jack Hessel Cornell University   Lily Hu Harvard University   Abigail Jacobs University of California Berkeley   Emmanuel Johnson University of Southern California   Sanmi Koyejo University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign   Hugo Larochelle Google Brain   Zachary C Lipton Carnegie Mellon University   Kristian Lum Human Rights and Data Analysis Group   Ciira Maina Dedan Kimathi University of Technology   Vukosi Marivate University of Pretoria   Margaret Mitchell Google AI   Nyalleng Moorosi None   George Musumba Dedan Kimathi University of Technology   Zanele Munyikwa MIT Sloan School of Management   Robert Ness Gamalon Inc   Ehi Nosakhare MIT   Billy Okal Voyage   Charles C Onu McGill University   Vicente Ordonez University of Virginia   Lonnie T Parker Naval Sea Systems Command   Forough Poursabzi-Sangdeh Microsoft Research   David Robinson Cornell University   Evan Rosenman Stanford University   Negar Rostamzadeh Element AI   Natalie Schluter IT University of Copenhagen   Flora Tasse University of Cambridge   Rachael Tatman Kaggle   Matthew Tesfaldet York University &amp;amp; Vector Institute of Artificial Intelligence   Alemu Leulseged Tesfaye Ca Foscari University of Venice   Kale-ab Tessera University of Witwatersrand   Rachel Thomas fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors 2018</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2018/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2018/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to our corporate sponsors, the workshop is free to attendees and we are able to provide inclusive travel funding to select participants.
 Diamond Sponsors --  Platinum Sponsors --  Gold Sponsors   Silver Sponsors   -- We thank the following companies for their support.
 Airbnb Kaggle   We also thank the following institutions for sponsoring their students to attend the workshop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submission Instructions 2018</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2018/submissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2018/submissions/</guid>
      <description>We welcome work in artificial intelligence, including, but not limited to, computer vision, deep learning, knowledge reasoning, machine learning, multi-agent systems, natural language processing, statistical reasoning, theory, robotics, as well as applications of AI to other domains such as health and education, and submissions concerning fairness, ethics, and transparency in AI. Papers may introduce new theory, methodology, or applications. We also welcome position papers and demos related to these areas. Work may be previously published, completed, or ongoing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Grants 2018</title>
      <link>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2018/grants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://esube.github.io/workshop/2018/grants/</guid>
      <description>Need-based travel grants will be awarded to workshop participants. Participants do not need to submit a paper in order to be considered for a travel grant. The travel grant can be used for covering costs associated with the workshop such as NIPS registration, accommodation and travel. Please note that the travel grants may not cover all of your costs and we may not be able to award them to all applicants.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>